In Clover Configurator go to Acpi Tab then DSDT section, Find Patches and type the following :
Comment: change GFX0 to IGPU
Find:    47465830
Replace: 49475055
Go to Boot Tab and be sure to check the -disablegfxfirmware checkbox if not checked already.
Go to Device Tab then Fake ID section, Find Intel GFX and delete existing value if any and type : 0x59168086
Now go to Graphics Tab and be sure to check the Inject intel Check Box if not checked already.
Now go to ig-platform-id and delete existing value if any and type : 0x59120000
Save your config.plist.
Reboot.


